# Milan Stevanović

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 

## **CONTACT DETAILS**

Address: Sadika Ramiza 32-100, Beograd, Serbia

Email: milan.stevanovic.ms3@gmail.com Linked: linkedin.com/in/milan-stevan0vic

## **EDUCATION**

University of Belgrade
Master's Degree, Computer Science
2008 - 2012

# **SKILLS**

Frontend Development
- React, Vue, Angular 2+, ElectronJs
- GraphQL, RESTful api
- Ant Design, TailwindCSS, SCSS, styled
components, Vuetify

#### **Backend Development**

- Node, Laravel
- Express, Nest

Database

- MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL

Cloud Services and APIs

- AWS, Firebase
- Stripe, Sendgrid

## **PROFILE**

Solution-driven Full Stack Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using PHP, JavaScript and Python. Built products for web, desktop and mobile app users over 7+ years, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Full Stack Developer**

Self-Employed | May 2021 - present

## **Full Stack Developer**

Codetribe | Jun 2018 - Apr 2021

- Developed multiples serverless web apps; using Node, React, AWS API Gateway, and AWS Lambda, EC2, Route 53.
- Developed an internal application using Vue/Nuxt, Tailwind and PHP, Laravel for Relationship Mangers.
- Migrated the project to an optimized AWS infrastructure.
- I developed many Websites and Mobile Apps for a variety of business using Javascript and JS framework (React/Node, RN, Angular)
- Through this period, I had learnt how vitally important good communication with customers is and also how to work efficiently and effectively from a remote location, among many other things.
- As part of international team, all working remotely, communication was key and as other developers in the company may need to work on the site code from time to time it was vital that all code be kept tidy, well commented, and regularly pushed to Git.

# Milan Stevanović

**FULL STACK DEVELOPER** 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Full Stack Developer**

AVS Solutions | Dec 2016 - Apr 2018

- Built rich SPAs using Vue/Nuxt, React, Angular.
- Developed with serverless Node.js and JavaScript
- Built RESTful APIs using a serverless framework
- Experienced with AWS EC2, Route53, Gateway, Cognito, Lambda, CloudFormation and AWS S3.
- Collaborated with other developers in an Agile environment, using Scrum methodology
- Started as a front-end developer and advanced to lead frontend developer

### **Full Stack Developer**

PanonIT | May 2013 - Oct 2016

- Integrated Google Maps API to implement the auto-complete search box feature.
- Developed responsive UI pages for the website
- Bought domain at Namecheap and configured DNS records to point to Netlify name servers.
- Designed the database schema and integrated the MySQL database with the website.